You were right .
This is definitely better than being at work .
One thing you didn 't warn us about though - - bloody midges .
You big girl 's blouse ! .
Anyway , now that you 've mentioned work
and seeing as I bullied you to come here to celebrate ...
Here .
Congratulations .
No knight should be without his sword .
I don 't know what to say .
What , my writer lost for words ? .
It 's perfect .
Yeah , and it 's also solid silver so don 't lose it !
Nice try , Private Cooper .
You 've evaded capture for twenty-two hours
and forty-seven minutes .
Go straight to the head of the class .
Of course , the real trick to survival
lies not in running and hiding
but in removing your enemy 's capacity to hunt you down .
Here . Shoot the dog .
I 'm sorry , sir , what ? .
Take the weapon and use it .
During the selection process , you are under my command !
That 's a direct order , Cooper !
You 're taking the piss , right ? .
He thinks I am pulling his leg . Do I Iook like a sodding soldier comedian , Shitwipe ? . !
No , sir !
I still won 't do it .
You don 't have a choice . Finish the job . Shoot the dog .
Shoot it !
No , sir !
What use are you to my team
if you can 't even kill a dog ? .
I didn 't say I couldn 't kill a dog , sir .
I just will not kill that dog for no reason .
You 're binned , Cooper .
- I don 't need a man of conscience . - You 're failing me for this ? .
You failed yourself !
We 're on a different level here , Cooper .
For that ...
I need men of action
not deeds .
No ! You sick fucking bastard !
It 's just a dog . That 's all .
Maybe one day when that 's sunk into your thick skull
you 'll be ready for us .
Until then , you live and learn .
Yeah , but you don 't .
I don 't do second chances , Cooper .
And I never forget .
RTU this pathetic piece of shit .
Send him back to his squad .
I want a good , clean dispersal .
I want a secure landing zone .
Go , go , go , go , go !
Joe , get out of the pissing chopper !
I 'm not missing the footy for this , it 's totally bone !
I 'm not going , sarge . I 'm not going !
See you .
Cooper ... I want a position and bearing .
- I want to be on the move in three minutes . - On it , Sarge .
Spoon , Terry , you 're on stag .
Joe , for fuck sake
get off your big , fat , Iardy arse and make like a soldier !
Right then - - time sync .
I 've got zero seven-thirty coming up in
three , two , one , check .
Oh bullocks , I don 't believe this !
What is it now , Witherspoon ? .
I 've left my watch at the barracks , sarge .
You want to take a breather every once in a while , son , you 'll live longer .
Nice work , Spoon , you tosser .
Took the words right out of my mouth .
And you 'II be taking my boot out your mouth in a minute , Joe , you baldy twat !
Pissing hell !
Close shave , eh Joe ? .
Oh , this shit is totally bone !
The most important football match of my life is playing tonight
and I 'm stuck up the backside of beyond without so much as
a six-pack or a telly !
Yeah , well , that 's the Army for you .
Hey , it 's England v Germany , man .
Full-on footy war !
Yeah , well , it 's nothing like this at all then , is it Joe ? .
It 's just an exercise . Hardly life or death .
Don 't bet on it , Joe , you 're fucking slaying me !
If you 'd paid any attention at all during the briefing , Kirkley
you 'd know exactly who we were up against on this harmless little exercise , wouldn 't you ? .
- And who 's that then ? . - Special Forces , you plonker !
Bollocks to them !
All right , all right .
Now listen up , I 'm gonna make this quick and to the point
because , just like you , all I wanna do is get home
jump into a warm bed with a nice hot woman and watch the footy !
Planning on scoring , sarge ? .
Yeah , well , mind you don 't foul her in the penalty box .
All right , button it , private parts !
Now , as of this moment as far as we 're concerned , we are fifty ' K ' behind enemy lines .
Now , if we do happen to make a contact
I expect nothing less than gratuitous violence from the lot of you .
Because we 're firing blanks
it doesn 't mean we have to be thinking ... nice thoughts .
So you remember you put the fire down , right ? .
You get stuck in and you kick their fucking teeth out
or I 'II guarantee you , Joe , they will be having your bollocks for breakfast , sunshine !
Hard-boiled or fried , sarge ? .
Scrambled .
Here you are , Spoonie .
Oh , smart .
Because it 's nice and new and shiny doesn 't mean it 's worth shit .
Remember I want that back , son .
What about you , sarge ? .
Well , I 'll count , won 't I ? .
Right then , Coop , what we got ? .
We 're here . The front line is here .
AWAC reports enemy positions here , here and here .
With sweeping patrols between each of these forward bunkers
they 'II have the whole sector wrapped tighter than an Eskimo 's nad-sack .
With one exception .
Right here .
A river crosses the line through a gorge
thirty or forty feet deep
and it 's certain to have a patrol on it , but if we go at night
tread careful and
don 't mind getting our feet wet
I reckon we can make it through .
What the fuck is all this about then ? .
Oh , with my luck lately , I need all of the help I can get .
I know you think it was a piss poor call ,
you failing selection and all of that , but
I gotta say , I 'm not sorry .
The squad would be a Iot worse off without you , mate .
It was something I had to do , you know .
For myself , get it out my system .
Listen , the only people who go looking for trouble are Kamikazes
glory boys and full-on fucking fuckwits !
Take my advice son , be patient .
Right then , ladies
pack up your troubles
put your brains in first gear and start tabbing !
Spoonie , you 're on point .
Terry , Joe , tail-end Charlies .
Over here , Cooper , on my head .
You twatter !
I can 't believe I 'm missing the footy for this party !
Joe , if you don 't shut up , I swear to God I 'm gonna fucking slot you myself !
- Now move ! . - Didn 't say a word , sarge .
Where the hell are we now ? .
I heard a cracking story about this place .
You what ? .
people disappear out here . Happens all the time .
Go on , Cooper , lad , give it some boolocks .
It 's true .
Just last month a young couple were hiking through these woods .
They set up camp somewhere near here . During the night - something happened .
A mountain rescue team found the remains of the camp a couple of days alter .
The tent was ripped to shreds and there was blood everywhere !
The papers said it was a monster like The Beast of Bodmin Moor .
Locals claimed it was an escaped lunatic .
But no-one 's been caught so nothing can be proved either way .
Every year more and more people come through here
and every one in a while they don 't come back .
No trace , no bodies - - just disappear
and never seen again .
Contact camp .
Tell them the flock is heading for the fold .
Broadsword to base .
Come on then , Bruce , what scares you ? .
The seIf-destructive nature of the human condition .
You 're just taking the piss now !
What , you think so ? .
What about you then , Spoon ? .
Castration .
There 's no argument there . Joe ? .
Joe , only one thing guaranteed to put the shits up me .
A penalty shoot out .
- Figures . - Terry ? .
Watching a penalty shoot out - - with Joe .
What about you , Coop ? .
Spiders - - And women .
And - - spider women .
I want to know what scares the sarge .
Piss off , man , nothing scares the sarge !
Oh , I don 't know about that .
well , the thought of never seeing my wife again scares the shit out of me !
That and those little things that make your skin crawl
and the hair stand up on the back of your neck .
You mean like Spoon ? .
No , there 's one thing actually , in particular
that I 'll remember till the day that I die .
Yeah , it was back in ninety-one ,
just before my unit was flown out to Kuwait
to mop up the last pockets of resistance .
Me and this young fella called Eddie Oswald
decided to go and get a tattoo done
to commemorate our first trip into the desert .
Yeah , I remember Eddie .
He was a stocky hard case
with a broken nose and a bong eye , yeah ? .
Yeah , that 's him . Good-Iooking fella . Big hit with the ladies .
Anyway , me and Eddie , we went and had a few drinks
we had a lot of drinks
then we went down to the tattoo parlour and I got a Deser Rat done
and Eddie being Eddie wanted something with a bit more meaning .
And being a bit of a believer
he said that his soul still belonged to God
but his flesh , well , his flesh was way beyond redemption
and it was up to Satan to save his skin .
So he got this fucking great laughing devil tattooed right on his arse .
Anyway , about six days later we were making a regular sweep along the Iraqi border
and Eddie , poor fucker , triggered an anti-tank mine .
Yeah . We all saw it happen . I mean , he was on point .
White blinding lightning flash and
a fucking deafening crack .
And by the time we picked ourselves up off the deck , Eddie was
he was gone .
Just bits and pieces of him . That 's all that remained .
This big fucking red circle . Hundred metres .
I 'II tell you something , lads , it really puts things in perspective
when you have to scoop your mate up with a shovel and
stick him in a bin-bag .
Anyway , the thing that
really did our nuts in that day was when you
came across a bit you recognised .
Bit of ear - - toe , a nose , a tooth .
But the thing that really freaked us out that day
was when Left Hand charlie found the bit of Eddie with the tattoo on .
I mean everything else was burnt to a crisp , covered in claret .
All mushed up , pulped up .
Not this bit . This bit was perfect .
And there 's old Nick chortIing his fucking arsehole off at us !
So you could say that Eddie was right
that Satan did indeed save his skin ,
just not all of it .
Or you cold say that Eddie was just unlucky .
Either way it taught me to keep a very open mind .
Boom boom .
Anyway ... Eddie Oswald .
- To Eddie . - To Eddie .
So , anyway , this bloke walks into a pub , right
with a little dog under his arm .
He puts it down on the bar , goes and sits down .
The bartender 's looking at him thinking
" What the fucking hell 's going on here ? " .
Then he looks back at the dog and ,
to his surprise , the dog turns round and says ...
It 's a fucking cow !
Fucking hell !
Ceasefire , Terry , ceasefire .
Terry , what the hell are you doing ? . You 're firing blanks , man !
Is everyone all right ? .
No man , I think I 've shit myself !
Is it dead ? .
Oh yeah , it 's dead all right .
- Christ , look at the state of it ! - Sod that , man , look at the state of Terry .
These aren 't entry wounds - - More like teeth marks .
What are you saying , Cooper ? .
What he 's saying , Terry , is it died of natural causes , mate .
Don 't you think we should call this in , sarge ? .
Aye , get on the radio , Bruce .
Now there 's no way I 'm about to break radio silence
because you lot got spooked by a dead flying fucking cow !
No , we hold this position . We keep it secure till the morning
then we reassess the situation .
Right , I want a watch posted .
Two on , four off .
Brucie , Spoon , you 're up first .
Cooper and I will relieve you at zero one hundred hours .
And in meantime - Terry sort your kit out !
The rest of you get your heads down .
Unbelievable .
Sarge ... cow came in from this direction
straight off the edge .
Out of the frying pan on to the fire .
Bleeding to death
it could have wandered around for miles before it got here .
Yeah , well , it 's good of it to leave some breadcrumbs for us to follow , eh ? .
- Looking for trouble ? . - No , Cooper - - just looking .
Sarge , shouldn 't we just report this when we get back ? .
Too fucking right , Terry . But in the meantime ,
I 'm curious and it 's on our way .
Come on , lads .
Natural causes , my arse .
Oh , now what ? .
Christ on a bike !
What the fucking hell happened here , sarge ? .
This is getting more bone by the minute !
Oh , Jesus Christ . Sarge !
Right , lads - - get a grip .
We 've got casualties to locate .
So , ditch your bergens , salvage whatever weapons you can find
and stand to .
We are now up against live hostile targets .
So if little Red Riding Hood should show up with a bazooka and a bad attitude
I expect you to chin the bitch !
Looks like they got hit hard and fast . Every magazine is full .
Nobody got off a single round .
If they lost , then where are the bodies ? .
All right , corporal
get on the net and call in . I want emergency airlift immediately !
I 'm on it .
- holy shit ! - Contact !
Help me !
Captain !
Ryan ? . ! What happened here ? .
Do not tell me you fucking know him ? .
Captain Ryan . Special Ops .
Not the fucking dog lover ? .
Spearhead Patrol , this is Spearhead Patrol .
Are you receiving ? .
He looks like he took on Jack the Ripper and came last !
I can patch him up but he needs a medic right now !
This is emergency Code 64 .
You 've gotta get me out of here ! Do you understand ? .
There was only supposed to be one !
We 're working on it , Captain !
- Sarge . - Not now , Spoon .
Are you receiving ? .
- Shit . - What 's wrong , Bruce ? .
I can 't find a signal !
Didn 't you check it ? .
Of course I checked it ! And I double checked it and it worked fine !
All right , Bruce , stay on it , see what you can do .
Terry
this team must have had their own coms kit . Have a look a round , see if you can find it . Go !
... have a shufti round the camp , see if you can find anything else useful .
- Yah , but ... - Not now , Spoon !
This is Spearhead Patrol . Are you receiving me ? .
There 's only supposed to be one !
Jesus ! Charnel House is compromised to fuck !
- Do you copy ? . - What the hell 's he doing here ? .
All I know is he 's Special Forces .
But if this is part of our exercise , they 're not advertising .
No cap badge , no insignia , just tags .
What , you mean it 's some kind of convert action ? .
Convert action or not ,
they 're packing all kind of weird shit !
Tranquillizer darts , nets
you name it .
This is less like a Special Ops mission
more like a fucking safari .
Sarge , I found their radio .
- Oh shit ! I don 't believe it !
There was only supposed to be one !
What 's he on about , sarge ? .
Terry , get back on stag now .
You 've got to get me out of here before they come back !
Who , captain ? . Who is going to come back ? .
They tore them to pieces in front of my eyes !
He 's off on one , sarge !
If we don 't get him somewhere warm soon , he 's gonna die of hypothermia !
Stay with me , captain .
Ryan , stay with me !
Not now , Spoon !
I don 't know if you care but in about half an hour it 's gonna be dark .
Does anybody copy ? .
- Any joy ? . - Fuses are blown .
Can you fix it ? .
well , maybe it was faulty or maybe some damp got in the casing , but it 's fried the circuits .
Well
it 's useless , mate , bin it .
I also found this .
It was attached inside . Not part of the radio .
Look like a transmitter .
Why would they put a bug in our radio ? .
it 's the Kobayashi Maru test .
They 've fixed it so we can 't fucking win !
Button it , Spoon !
No , Terry , it 's probably some joker didn 't want .
Joe to hear the footy results .
Laugh ? . I nearly shat !
Can we scrounge anything useful ? .
Weapons , ammunition
couple of magnesium flares .
That 's about it . The rest 's fucked !
Right , lads ditch your 80s . From here on in the exercise is well and truly over .
Anyone not carrying live rounds had better do so .
it won 't make any difference .
- They won 't die . - Yeah , well ...
- .. this gives me better peace of mind , sir .
You want peace of mind
run for your lives before they tear your legs from under you !
Now you just shut up like a good gentleman !
You are scaring my lads .
What the fuck ... !
Oh Christ !
- Oh , Shit ! - All right , lads grab what you can
head for the tree line . We 're moving . Let 's go .
Right , I need a volunteer for rearguard action .
- I 'II do it . - Nice one . When we 're clear , you fall back .
We 're gonna be there to cover you . Right , off you go !
Bruce - - no heroics .
Right , Spoonie , you 're on point !
Joe , help Ryan . Terry , you 're up next .
Coop , you 're with me !
Right , lads ,
let 's have it through the Iong grass ! Double time ! Go !
Come on , sunshine , fucking shift it !
Come on !
Oh , shit !
Bruce . Bruce !
Cooper , get out of it !
Incoming !
Coming up on both rear flanks !
- To your rear ! - Target !
- Coming through . - Target !
Keep moving !
Covering fire !
They 're going for a flanking position !
They 're cirling us !
Covering fire !
Coming through !
Target !
Covering fire !
Reload !
Fucking get out !
Just fucking leg it !
Target !
Lads !
On me ! On me !
Stop !
Get in !
- Everybody on me ! - Hurry !
Company , fire !
In ! In ! In !
Safety !
Oh , shit !
Just drive !
Now !
I 'm trying !
Fucking floor it !
Joe , stab it !
Try reverse .
Stab it , Joe !
Now forward .
Everybody okay back there ? .
Any more casualties ? . Spoon ? .
- No , I 'm all right . - What about Bruce ? .
- Where 's Bruce ? . - Bruce is gone !
He 's gone !
Oh , fuck it !
Just hang on back there !
Thank you .
That 's okay . What happened ? .
What happened ? . We were attacked by huge fucking howling things ! That 's what !
You were lucky I found you .
I was about to give up hope .
You knew we were here ? .
I heard gunfire last night .
I knew someone was out there .
If you weren 't already in trouble , then you soon would be .
We are - - Two men are down .
Both need medical attention .
We need to dress the sarge 's wounds
before we can take him too far .
There 's only one farm in this glen , but
the owner are friends .
We can take your men there .
Hello .
- Nobody home ? . - I don 't know where they could be .
Right .
Stand back .
Little pigs , little pigs - -
we 've come to nick your video !
You sit .
Sit . Sit .
You stay .
All clear .
- What the fuck happened back there , Copper ? . - I don 't know , mate .
She might have some answers .
All clear upstairs .
Where the hell are we now ? .
Home sweet home .
Set him down .
Spoon , get a field dressing on that wound .
Terry , keep an eye out front .
Come on .
Shit !
What are you doing to me ? .
- Is there a telephone here ? . - What ? . No .
Still hot , lads .
Wait . You can 't just help yourself !
I 'm chin-strap and I 'm bloody starving .
I can 't help myself .
It 's the training , miss . Never waste an opportunity to eat . Come on .
See
now look what I 'm doing !
Get it down your necks , lads .
Hold it . Hold it .
Top grub . What is it ? .
Don 't know , ( mate ) . Looks like pork .
Yeah , well , leave some for us , you greedy mongrels !
Miss , where is the nearest phone ? .
Fifty miles as the crows flies .
What about the nearest population centre ? .
You mean a town ? .
well , Fort william but it 's at Ieast four hour drive back the way we just came .
Do you think your wounded can make it ? .
We have to try . The sarge is in serious trouble if we don 't .
You seem to know these roads .
- will you take us ? . - Right now ? .
well , unless you friends have just gone walkabout , this place may be compromised .
Fine . Sooner the better .
Let 's go .
Right . Spoon , on me .
Everyone else , hang back till we bring the car about .
Joe , help sarge .
Terry , watch him .
Safeties off .
Don 't shoot .
Don 't stare back .
I can 't help it .
Go !
Come on !
Cooper , have you gone spare or what ? .
- Cooper , you radgie ! - That puts the kibosh on that plan !
That was my car !
Give us a fucking hand here !
Oh my God !
Fuck off !
Fuck that !
Stand back !
Bloody hell !
Go on , son !
What the fucking hell 's happening ? .
Terry , right flank . Cover the window !
For Christ 's sake , Terry , man , get a grip !
That 's bloody charming , that is !
You incompetent moron !
Do you want to have a fucking go , like ? . !
Bathroom ? .
Upstairs . Far end of passage .
We need to talk , Ryan .
Doesn 't look like I 'm going anywhere , does it ? . !
Joe , Spoon , look like we 're staying .
You know what to do .
I want a secure perimeter with a clear field of fire .
But give them something inviting .
Right ? . - I 'm on it .
Terry , are you okay ? .
- I 've got a real craving for a kebab . - I 'll take that as a yes .
Right , we 've got limited ammunition .
I want you to get as many pots and pans as you can lay your hands on
fill them with water and keep them on the boil , all right ? .
Terry
while you 're at it , stick the kettle on . We could all do with a brew .
Terry give us a hand with this .
Other side . Other side . Ah , you fool !
You came here because of them , right ? .
I don 't have a fucking clue what ' they ' are .
And right now , I don 't really care .
Then what are you doing here ? .
This was supposed to be a routine training exercise and that 's all .
So this wasn 't a rescue mission ? .
No , I guess not .
Back door 's secure .
What 's happening here , Spoon ? .
Well , they 're still moving around our there
but they 're keeping their distance , staying within the tree line .
Maybe they 've had enough for one night .
Not likely .
They 're smart . You 've seen what they can do .
My guess
is they 're doing exactly what you 'd be doing in their shoes .
They 're working as a team . Looking for a weakness , a way in .
I 'm not about to second guess these things .
They 're enemy , simple as that .
This is no ordinary enemy .
You know what this reminds me of ? .
Rourke 's Drift .
A hundred men of HarIech making a desperate stand
against ten thousand Zulu warriors .
Outnumbered , surrounded
staring death in the face , not flinching for a moment .
Balls of British steel .
You 're bloody loving this , aren 't you ? .
It 's totally bone - - That 's all there is to say .
So , what are we talking about here , wolves ? .
Not entirely wolf . Not all human ,
but something in between .
Wolfmen ? . You 're having a laugh , right ? .
I may be nuts but I 'm not fruitcake !
Fine . Stay here and drink tea !
I thought you might be here because of them , but I guess not .
Just don 't be an arsehole !
I like your new girlfriend , Coop .
How are you feeling ? .
A touch of gas .
And the fact that various body parts are trying to vacate the premises
fucking awful !
- It 's hot . - Cheers .
Heads up !
For crying out loud , man !
Short controlled bursts !
Do you have a name , soldier ? .
Cooper .
Gonna need your help here , miss .
My name is Megan .
And I know how to kill them .
Shit , sarge , you 're leaking like a sieve !
Look , I need you to get some superglue and some whisky , all right ? .
I 'll see what I can do .
- Come on . - No , no , no ...
sorry about the arsehole thing . I 've got a mean streak a mile across .
That 's all right . It 's the least of my worries right now .
Can you pass me my gun , please ? .
Thank you .
Come on , Coop , up the wooden hill .
- Where are we going , Coop ? . - You don 't wish to know , mate .
What 's the glue for ? .
Ever wondered why the best thing that
superglue sticks together is your fingers ? .
- Fucking get off ! - Give it . Give it .
Forget your grandma 's china cups
this stuff was developed for the Vietnam war to patch up broken soldiers .
How are you feeling , sarge ? .
Absolutely fucking top fucking bollocks !
Are you sure he should be chasing painkillers with whisky ? .
Yeah , well , he 's earned it .
- Is it your birthday , Coop ? . - No , mate .
Is it my birthday ? .
No , but you 're gonna thank us for this in the morning .
I 'll tell you something , mate ,
I 'm gonna fucking thank you right now .
I 'm gonna thank you because you saved my Iife . You got me out of there , mate .
Yeah , well , you would have done the same thing .
If I 'd done the same fucking thing ,
I would have saved Bruce - - wouldn 't I ? .
Yeah , fuck !
Sausages !
I 'll tell you something , miss , right
this geezer here , right , is my best mate .
He 's the salt of the fucking earth .
I mean , don 't get me wrong , the rest of the geezers in the squad , they 're all right ,
lovely fellas and stuff
and any single one of them could marry my
marry my sister - - if I had one .
I 'll tell you what , I love him . I love you
like a mate that I ... that I love .
Would you like to be alone ? .
Oh , you - - dirty fucker !
Here .
- It 's the adrenaline . - I 'll stick , you bond .
I 'II tell you something , someone better get fucking stuck in soon
because this is really starting to hurt !
- What 's up ? . - Cooper , knock me out . Hit me !
Oh you fucking pussy , hit me ...
Go , go .
- So , how long have you lived round here ? . - Two years .
Came here for wildlife .
I 'm a zoologist .
So , you 've heard those stories as well then .
Yeah , I heard the stories , I went looking , I found evidence .
- I was fascinated by the possibility that ... - You can 't seriously believe in werewolves ? .
Straight out of college , I 'd have laughed at the suggestion , but now
I know they 're as real as you and me .
Before tonight is over , you will too .
There - - I think that will hold .
- You done this before ? . - Oh , yeah .
We glue people 's gut together all the time out here .
Everyone tooled up ? .
To the nines .
You 'll have a fucking eye out with that , lad .
Right , Terry , look sharp !
The rest of you
I know things have gone from shit to bone
to worse in the last twenty four hours , but
if we pull our weight and do the job
we still have a fighting chance . No more running .
We stand , here . We fight .
Right ? . - - Any questions ? .
Oh , just the one , Coop . Exactly what is it we 're fighting against ? .
Megan ? . You want to run it past the boys ? .
- Lycanthropes . - You what ? .
That 's werewolves to you and me .
- You 're taking the piss ? . - What ? . Makes perfect sense to me !
What , you mean like full moons ,
silver bullets and eyebrows that join in the middle ? .
Before you dismiss it offhand ,
think about what you 've seen and heard .
The full moon , the teeth
the claws , the howling . Is it so difficult to believe ? .
For a whole year now
I 've tracked these things .
I 've studied them . Tried to understand them .
Ever month , when the moon is full
they hunt as a team . Dedicated to the kill .
During that time , at Ieast fifteen people have vanished .
Hikers mostly . In small groups or alone .
They 're caught out in the open , hunted down ,
torn apart and devoured .
I 've never witness the actual slaughter , but the next day
no bodies , no werewolves - - just blood .
The eyebrow 's thing is nonsense .
It 's just Dark Age paranoia . And silver bullets
no-one 's ever get close enough to try .
I 'm sold .
Slow down , Spoon , but Megan may have a point .
I 'm still not convinced
that these things didn 't just escape from the local nuthouse
and forget to shave or trim their nails .
But they 're out there and we 're in here .
What they may or may not be
does not affect our immediate situation one bit .
This is bone .
This is so fucking bone !
Anything else ? .
Yeah , what does bone mean ? .
Bone - bollocks . Naff .
Not very good .
Right . Anything else I should know ? .
Call-signs . If you need to be specific .
Upstairs , you 've got Sergeant wells who you seem to know inside and out by now .
You 've got Spoon over there .
The vomiting cavalier , Terry .
The big guy with the axe is Joe .
Didn 't you forget someone ? .
Ryan .
Captain Ryan is not one of our team .
His being here is hazy at best .
If I could tell you , I would .
But I 'm just a soldier - - like you .
No stripes - - no insignia .
A suit in a uniform does not make a soldier .
He 's with Special Ops .
His team were wiped out last night . He was the only survivor .
I 'd advise you against pursuing this line of questioning , Private Cooper .
Are you pulling ranks on me now , captain ? .
You can shove that right up your arse !
I 'm saying my being here is a most point
since I 'm now in as much shit as you are .
We 're all in the same fucking shit .
And we need each other .
I doubt I need you .
You bloody did two hours ago !
The Uaths .
Crying like a baby , you were .
That was then . Circumstances change .
What ? .
Uath - it 's Celtic .
The family has lived in this glen for centuries .
So , what was he doing out there ? .
I have an idea .
But I want to hear it from the horse 's mouth .
Come to think of it , Ryan , how are you feeling ? .
I 'm fine .
When we found you ,
you could barely open your eyes , let alone walk
and then later , you managed to run
and now look at you - fighting fit and sitting pretty .
Hardly the behaviour of a man who
until recently , was knocking on death 's door .
I have a strong constitution .
You 're not bloody kidding !
Then you won 't mind if I have a look at that wound of yours .
I 'd just as soon you didn 't .
I have a responsibility to my patient .
I 'm warning you , Cooper , don 't touch me !
Get back !
Tie him up . I want him to talk .
- What are you gonna do , torture him ? . - Don 't know .
- What would you do ? . - I 'd torture him .
What now ? . !
They 've shut down the generator . - Why would they do that ? .
Because they can see in the dark .
And you 're afraid of it .
This is a pile of rancid shit !
Now what do you believe ? .
I 'm beginning to believe you ,
but I think Joe might have worded it better .
They 're on the move !
All right this is it !
Mark your targets and preserve your ammo .
Three round bursts .
We 've only got one stun grenade apiece
so only use them if absolutely necessary .
- Stand to . - Come on then .
- What can I do ? . - What do you want to do ? .
Run and hide . I know what 's coming .
Take care of Sam .
Keep an eye on Ryan . If he tries anything , pan him .
Chasing that first kiss , are we , Cooper ? .
It 's as simple as this .
If you 're not there for us
we 're not here for you .
Contact !
Die !
Spoon , get down !
Fucking back !
Fuck !
Fire in the hole !
Cooper ! ... Hurry !
Cheers , mate .
Sarge .
Cooper !
Sarge ! ... Sarge !
Bastard !
Sarge , wake up !
Fucking wake up , you bastard !
Sarge ! Say ' cheese ' , you fucker !
Wake up !
Fuck ! Sarge !
Dogs ? . More like pussies !
You all right ? .
Oh , yeah , yeah , I 'm peachy , mate .
Coop ... squad 's yours , mate .
They took Terry .
Then we go and get him back !
Too fucking right !
Forget about him .
What did you say ? .
He 's dead , Cooper , and you know it .
Shit !
Somebody must have heard some gunfire !
- Somebody must have heard something ! - Who ? .
The only other house within fifty miles of here is mine . And I ' , not there !
Well , what about the road , man ? . Passers-by ? .
Do you have any idea what kind of luck you had
running into me out there tonight ? .
I thought you ran into us ? .
Joe , check upstairs .
Even if anyone did come by , they would only end up
lambs for the slaughter like you .
Our only hope is daylight .
The sun rises in six hours .
We did the best we could .
But if the sarge 's condition deteriorates
he 'll have less than four .
And the only thing holding them back
is they don 't know how much ammunition we have left .
Let 's have a look at that .
Tell me . Honestly , what are our chances ? .
Morale seems good , considering .
But that will only last
as long as the ammunition holds out .
High spirits are just no substitute of eight hundred rounds a minute
but I don 't think that 's what you wanted to hear .
Think about it , Cooper - up until today
you believe there was a line between myth and reality .
May have been a very fine line sometimes ,
but - - at least there was a line .
Those things out there are real .
And if they 're real , what else is real ? .
You know what lives in the shadows now .
You may never get another night 's sleep as long as you live .
So , why worry , Cooper ? . You may not live that long .
Shut your mouth !
We are gonna make it through this . You know why ? .
I don 't scare that easy .
Here .
It 's supposed to be lucky .
For me , or the rest of the rabbit ? .
- You 'll need a lot more than luck this time .
Shut up , Ryan !
Listen to me , Cooper
ignore him . We can survive till sunrise .
That 's all that matters .
- It 's just a few more hours .
Wait a minute . Am I missing something here ? .
I know him .
I was seconded to his team
during their first visit here .
First visit ? . What first visit ? . What the fuck are you talking about ? .
They came to check out the stories .
They needed an expert .
It 's just a few more hours , Cooper .
That 's all it is .
All clear ? .
- Yeah . - You wanna kill them all ? .
- Yes . - Good . Keep it up .
What 's the damage , Spoon ? .
Well , we might have pissed on our chips .
We 've only got two full mags for MP5s
six rounds for the shotgun
and one spare , just in case .
Stay sharp , everyone .
We were putting fire down all over .
I mean , we filled those things with lead and they just kept on getting up and coming back at us .
Sixty rounds , man , ain 't gonna last two minutes .
So , either we all make a break for it and fight our way clear or
or the rest of us keep them occupied
while one of us goes for help .
And by the time the cavalry get here
they 'II have to pick what 's left of us from between their fucking teeth !
Fucking brilliant !
We either stay and snuff it or we all go - -
and snuff it !
Decisions , decisions .
Laugh ? .
- I nearly died . - Who 's stopping you ? .
Right , that 's it !
We 'll fucking have him !
Take it easy , big man . Calm down .
Do any of you know how to hot-wire a car ? . What ? .
They keep an old Land Rover in the barn .
I don 't know where the keys are
but if one of you could break in and start it , then ...
I can do that .
- Are you sure ? . - Piece of piss !
Anyway , the further I am from this wanker , the happier I 'll be .
All right you 're gonna need a decoy .
Something fast and loud .
What ? . You what ? .
You sit . Stay .
- You 're serious about this werewolf thing , aren 't you ? . - I 'm afraid so .
Shit .
Don 't suppose you know who won the match .
Didn 't even know there was a game on .
It 's not a game .
Right , this is it .
Everyone get ready .
Bollocks .
Joe good luck , mate .
You don 't get off the hook that easy .
All right , you bastards
come and have a go if you think you 're hard enough !
Well , come on , you beauties !
They took the bait !
Come on !
Spoon , run !
Move your fucking arse , soldier !
Come on !
I 'm trying !
Pull us !
I love it when a posh bird talks dirty !
Jesus !
Fucking what 's happening , Cooper ? . !
Fucking cut it !
Get back !
Cut it !
- Cut it ! - Fucking thing !
Shit !
He 's done it ! Ryan , up ! Everyone else , downstairs .
- Come on , move it ! Come on ! - All right , Coop !
Move . Move .
You 're behind me , aren 't you ? .
I 'm gonna fucking have you !
Come on .
Ready ? . Go , go !
Back !
- well ? . - She 's in a bad way . Fuel pump 's gone
fan belt 's buggered and she 's pissing out petrol like there 's no tomorrow .
The word ' bone ' springs to mind .
Joe 's body ? .
It 's gone .
What 's the damage , Spoon ? .
We 're down to forty-eight rounds .
Check the right .
Well , Ryan - - you heard the score .
Maybe one or two of us are gonna make it through this
but I don 't care much for our chances .
You like football ? .
What ? . " They think it 's all over "
and all that crap ? .
No , I don 't .
Well , Joe ... you remember Joe ? .
He liked football . Fucking lived for it .
Is this relevant ? .
He missed the most important match of his life for this bullshit exercise
and now he 's dead along with two other mates
that I 'd have readily given my right arm for !
Too fucking right it 's relevant !
You just can 't get past the dog , can you ? .
We 're losing , Ryan . We 're three-niI down and we 're close to the final whistle .
At the very least , I want to even the score .
I understand your resentment .
But you failed
because you weren 't prepared to take that extra step .
If you 'd passed , you would have been on my team
and if you were on my team , you 'd be dead .
Yeah , I failed , and I 'm bloody glad of it .
Because given the choice of taking orders from a toffee-nosed twat like you
and slogging it out with these guys -
I 'll take the underdogs any time .
So you can take your precious selection , shove it up your arse
and stop trying to change the fucking subject !
Fair enough .
But you won 't like what I have to tell you .
There are some places you really shouldn 't go .
We 'll be the judge of that , Ryan .
Ever heard of Special Weapons Division ? .
They 're the men in white coats
who trains dolphins to stick mines on submarines
and cute furry animals
to tear your head off at the neck .
They saw an opportunity and called me in .
To do what ? . Catch one of these things ? .
And to bring it back - alive , if possible .
Only ' it ' turned out to be ' them ' .
- We underestimated enemy numbers . - Underestimated ? .
I 'd have a serious word with your head sheds
about the quality of their intelligence .
It may have been their invitation , but it was my party .
I planned and executed it .
You mean you loused it up .
We lost good men , Ryan . Yours
and mine .
I wanna know
where we fit in .
The reality is you 're expendable .
And I had approval to put you at risk .
Get to the fucking point , Ryan .
I made a gap in enemy lines .
You were good enough to spot it
and predictable enough to go for it . That was your bait .
You were mine .
You bastard !
I had to choose somebody .
I remembered you .
Monkey see , monkey do .
They were my men !
Get up , you shit . You know what we can do .
Give us a fighting chance .
Live and learn , Cooper .
I didn 't hit him that hard .
You shook something loose .
Bad dog .
Fetch !
Bag the shot !
Clear !
Get off !
Cooper , get down !
I 've got target !
WerewoIves spend most of the time in human form , right ? .
And the only people from miles around live right here .
So these things aren 't about to give up the fight and go home .
- They are home . - Yeah , well , that makes perfect sense , doesn 't it ? .
I mean , think about it -
we bust into their house ,
we eat all their porridge we sleep in their fucking beds .
no wonder they 're pissed off .
But they 're good people , they 're kind people .
- More 's a pity . - Why ? .
Because we 're gonna have to kill them all .
Too right , mate .
What self-respecting werewolf would have
anything silver in the house anyway ? .
Yeah , well , fuck the folklore
It 's just burn them .
If we knew where to find them .
Maybe we do .
Everything we 've seen so far suggests
the behaviour of a pack .
Six to eight members , an Alpha pair leading the subordinates
and a young male , a beta wolf ,
second in command , Makes sense .
No , you lost me .
A wolf pack sticks together . Generally somewhere close to its food supply .
Somewhere safe , sheltered - -
and warm .
You 're gonna have to move like shit off a shovel on this one , mate .
You worry about your own shit , all right ? .
When we blow that fuse that place is gonna go up like Zabriskie Point .
- Just make it work . - Yeah , it 's easy-peasy .
Yeah , lemon squeezy .
Listen , Coop ... what about the sarge ? .
What about the sarge ? .
You know what I mean .
Sarge is with us .
Yeah , I just didn 't want him to go
without getting his watch back .
You - - stay out of trouble .
You all right ? .
Oh , yeah , yeah , I 'm fine - - Cooper .
I mean , I feel
absolutely fantastic .
I mean , that 's the problem , isn 't it - -eh ? .
What if she 's wrong ? .
What if they 're not all in there , eh ? .
Then we only get some of them .
It 's a shit-load better than none of them
and marked improvement on all of us .
No , no , no , you listen to me .
You get the fuck out now .
I hold them back , I keep them occupied and you get out !
We 've lost enough men for on night , don 't you think ? .
Let me show you something .
Now do not tell me that that is fucking normal .
What happened to Ryan is happening to me .
It 's just a matter of time , mate .
Yeah , well , stop wasting time with this hara-kiri crap .
This fight isn 't lost yet .
With Ryan it only took a couple of hours , mate . It 's a full moon .
I mean , I dunno , maybe it 's like when you need to take a piss or something .
When you gotta go , you gotta fucking go .
Or maybe it 's more like needing a shite .
Just because you need one doesn 't mean you drop your legs and pinch one off .
Anyway , fuck Ryan .
Shifty bastard could 've been one of those things from the start .
You know , Coop , there 's one more thing you gotta learn about command , mate .
Sometimes the people that you kill - - are your own men .
So I 'm asking you let me take care of myself .
And at least spare you the
unfortunate business of trying to explain to Annie why you had to incinerate me .
We are gonna knock seven colours of shit out of these fuckers , we need you .
It 's all right , you know , mate .
It 's okay .
I just didn 't make it out this time , that 's all .
It goes with the job , do you know what I mean ? .
When I signed my Iife away on that dotted line , I fucking meant it !
I am a professional soldier !
So , what do you want me to do ? .
Roast their bollocks off .
All clear .
Good luck .
Light it !
Shit !
Sarge !
I 'm sorry .
When I found you out there tonight
I truly believed you were the best chance I had of getting out .
But now we have no chance .
There is no out .
There never was .
I came here to be at one with nature -
well , I got what I wanted .
Now I have to live with it .
- There isn 't a house in the next glen . - No .
And there were no werewolves in the barn when I blew .
Not one .
And the reason you 're not in the photograph is because you took it .
I never meant to ...
New woman - - same old shit .
Being nice to women will get you nowhere , Cooper .
Being nice to me will get you killed .
You may think they 're all bitches , but
I 'm the real thing .
Do you think I Iike being part of this fucked up family ? .
Do you think I chose to run with the pack ? .
No . I chose you .
But now you 're out of luck , and I 'm out of time .
And all we can do is let nature take its course .
They were always here
I just unlocked the door .
It 's that time of the month .
Somebody had to put it out of its misery .
Come on , Spoon !
Get clear !
Spoonie , stop fucking about !
Fucking shift it , that 's an order !
Oh , shit !
Shit !
Come on !
Sarge ? .
I 'm in the carzey .
Come on !
Oh Jesus ! Shit !
Go on , Coop ! Get stuck in , mate !
Get out of it !
Come on , you fucker !
Come on , come on !
- Cooper , Let 's get in the wardrobe , son . - What ? .
- Let 's get in the wardrobe . - Yeah , all right .
What 's that smell ? .
I dunno .
Fucking hell !
Give me your gun .
Open your mouth , watch your ears ,
mind your toes !
Go ! Go on !
Where 's Spoon ? . !
There is no Spoon .
- No , you fucking bastards ! - Help me , Cooper .
- Get in there . Get in there ! - Sam .
What are you doing ? . !
- Here , take this .
There 's one in the chamber , mate . I 'm fucking binned !
No , No ... We go together or we don 't fucking go !
That 's my last order to you , Do not fuck about . Do not disobey me !
Come here , you fucking ...
Listen to me , you have got to make it out alive .
It happened . Prove it happened !
Not just for me or my lads
for her !
Here ...
You have to prove it happened , mate .
Go ! Go !
Sam .
Fuck !
Ryan .
You tried licking your own balls yet ? .
I forgot - - you don 't fucking have any .
Think it 's all over ? .
It is now .
WEREWOLVES ATE MY PLATOON !
ENGLAND 5 GERMANY 1 TEAM BOUNCE BACK ABROAD !